<contentList date="17/08/2023 10:00">
  <content contentuid="h354d66e0g185eg4a38g805aga9caa11f17f6" version="1">POTION</content> 
  <content contentuid="h0d86d257g57e0g48a4gbe06g222ecf9d1e31" version="1">EXPLOSIVE</content> 
  <content contentuid="hafb1f446g2b90g4517gb022ge9c64254d39f" version="1">ARROW</content> 
  <content contentuid="h349b901eg3fceg413fg9f49g93914c5de462" version="1">COATING</content> 
  <content contentuid="he43abeaegb7bfg41b2g9263g390bf0710783" version="1">SCROLL</content> 
  <content contentuid="h720e20e2g9395g47d1g8970gc93efe112f8a" version="1">BOOK</content> 

  <content contentuid="ha24fd612ga6e5g4226g952bge3daa1bf5f14" version="1">Autosort Containers</content> 
  <content contentuid="hda39471eg7896g48b7ga531gbc5f2271c798" version="1">Whispering Wylde Quiver</content> 
  <content contentuid="h29545ebegdc58g411dg80a8g576b426ee178" version="1">Arcane Codex of Ethereal Enscrollments</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c33d2c5g50a7g486cg9f65gc92dd51e01ab" version="1">Eclipsian Phialmantle</content> 
  <content contentuid="hded932e3g534bg4b2ega375gd289e8c0f150" version="1">Flamewrought Mischiefkin</content>
  <content contentuid="hcdad16c7g7ee2g4553g98e7g1eb889084d0c" version="1">Nocentia Viperflask</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9fad078g4407g4456ga2e0g43d04179498f" version="1">Stores your arrows</content> 
  <content contentuid="h31d34ad0g8038g449fgb090g393f4253c84c" version="1">Stores your scrolls</content>
  <content contentuid="hec42cec7g475dg4a12g92cbg793218ea5123" version="1">Stores your potions</content> 
  <content contentuid="h3b89156fg1df9g4e6dga2a4gd174033c451b" version="1">Stores your grenades</content>
  <content contentuid="heea96ad2gd770g4071g9741ga34b5fce5dd6" version="1">Stores your weapon coatings</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c3837c4g2d41g440aga302g3a986c847daa" version="1">Autosorting containers for your arrows, scrolls, grenades, letters, books, weapon coatings and potions.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc994caa3gd163g468bg81b6g5ff50b7bee42" version="1">Behold the Whispering Wylde Quiver, a creation born of eldritch enchantments and woven from the essence of starlight itself. Its supple, obsidian-hued leather bears delicate traceries, akin to arcane sigils, embossed in glistening silver thread. The quiver's form undulates with an otherworldly grace, reminiscent of the fluid dance of willow branches in a moonlit glen.</content> 
  <content contentuid="heef64c1egf416g4b05ga73cg20abcb5ba7b5" version="1">Behold the Arcane Codex of Ethereal Enscrollments, a treasure trove of mystical wisdom encased in an exquisite relic forged from the heartwood of the Eldertree, a species entwined with the very fabric of magic. Its lacquered exterior shimmers with a myriad of colors, reminiscent of the auroras that grace the skies of a realm untouched by mortal feet.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08721676g3e3bg40a9g8887g79cd6ed61103" version="1">Behold the Eclipsian Phialmantle, a wondrous creation spun from the threads of dreams and dewdrops, a vessel that cradles the very essence of arcane elixirs. Crafted by the hands of twilight-forged artisans and blessed by celestial sages, this pouch is a masterpiece of both form and function, a tapestry of enchantment woven into every fiber.</content> 
  <content contentuid="hdae698e2ga1dag41bdgbb85gc1ae49c36988" version="1">Behold the Flamewrought Mischiefkin, a diminutive marvel of mischief sculpted from the very essence of infernos and laughter. With a form hewn from molten ruby and eyes that glint like mischievous stars, this sprightly creature dances upon the precipice between chaos and charm, a companion that defies expectations and ignites the heart with wonder.</content>
  <content contentuid="h16eb3747gc973g4f09ga6c0ge38cfec1adf3" version="1">Behold the Nocentia Viperflask, a mesmerizing vessel of potent malevolence, a masterpiece of the shadowed arts that cradles the essence of venoms both lethal and nefariously enchanting. Crafted from obsidian glass infused with the darkest secrets of the arcane, its sleek surface shimmers with a subtle iridescence, reminiscent of moonlight glinting upon a pool of midnight.</content>
</contentList>